http://www.mkttl.co.uk/info/privacy

Division Six
Doubles (Individuals)
Division Six
Doubles (Pairs)
Division Six
Doubles (Teams)
Division Six
Doubles (Individuals)
Division Six
Doubles (Pairs)
Division Six
Doubles (Teams)
Division Six
Doubles (Individuals)
Division Six
Doubles (Pairs)
Division Six
Doubles (Teams)
Division Seven
Doubles (Individuals)
Division Seven
Doubles (Pairs)
Division Seven
Doubles (Teams)
Division Seven
Doubles (Individuals)
Division Seven
Doubles (Pairs)
Division Seven
Doubles (Teams)
About this Policy
This policy explains when and why we collect personal information about our members, how we use it and how we keep it secure and your rights in relation to it.
We may collect, use and store your personal data, as described in this Data Privacy Policy and as described when we collect data from you.
We reserve the right to amend this Data Privacy Policy from time to time without prior notice. We may be required to amend this Data Privacy Policy due to regulations. For any significant changes you will be notified but you are advised to check www.mkttl.co.uk  for the latest Privacy Policy
We will always comply with the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) when dealing with your personal data.  Further details on the GDPR can be found at the website for the Information Commissioner (www.ico.gov.uk).  For the purposes of the GDPR, we will be the “controller” of all personal data we hold about you.
Who are we?
We are The Milton Keynes Table Tennis league.  We can be contacted via the Chairman or Secretary whose details appear on our website or in our Handbook.
What information we collect and why.
Member's name, address,
telephone numbers,
e-mail, address(es).
Managing the Member’s
membership of the
National Governing
Body and Ourselves
Performing the League’s contract with the Member.
For the purposes of our
legitimate interests in
operating the League.
Emergency contact details
Contacting next of kin in
the event of an
emergency
Protecting the Member’s vital interests and those of their dependents
Date of birth / age related
information
Managing membership
categories which are
age related
Performing the
League’s contract
with the member
Gender
Provision of adequate facilities for members
Reporting Information to
Table Tennis England
For the purposes of our
legitimate interests in making
sure we can provide sufficient and suitable facilities (including changing rooms and toilets) for each gender
For the purposes of the legitimate interests of Table Tennis England to maintain diversity data required by funders
The Member’s name, TTID
Managing competition
and event entries and
results
Publishing
results and ranking
For the purposes of our
legitimate interests in holding
competitions and events for
the benefit of members.  For the purposes of our legitimate interests in promoting the League
For the legitimate interest to providing relevant tournament and player information to Table Tennis England and providing communications to players
Photos and videos of
members
Putting on the website
and social media pages
and using in press
releases
Consent. We will seek the
consent on their membership
application form and each
membership renewal form.
The member may withdraw
their consent at any time by
contacting us by e-mail or
letter
Member’s name and
e-mail address
Creating and managing
key members
information and communication
Performing the League’s contract with the Member.
For the purposes of our
legitimate interests in
operating the League
Bank account details of
the member or other
person making payment to
Table Tennis England
None of the details are maintained by the League and we do not have access to details maintained by Table Tennis England
N/A to the League
Member’s and former
member’s name and e-
mail address
To conduct surveys of
Members and former
members for the benefit
of the League and
other legitimate contact
For the purposes of our
legitimate interests in
operating the League
How we protect your personal data
We will not transfer your personal data outside the EU without your consent.
We have implemented generally accepted standards of technology and operational security in order to protect personal data from loss, misuse, or unauthorised alteration or destruction.
Please note however that where you are transmitting information to us over the internet this can never be guaranteed to be 100% secure.
We will notify you promptly in the event of any breach of your personal data which might expose you to serious risk.
Who else has access to the information you provide us?
We will never sell your personal data. We will not share your personal data with any third parties without your prior consent (which you are free to withhold) except where required to do so by law or as set out in the table above or paragraph 5.2 below.
We may pass your personal data to third parties who are service providers, agents and subcontractors to us for the purposes of completing tasks and providing services to you on our behalf (e.g. to print newsletters and send you mailings).  However, we disclose only the personal data that is necessary for the third party to deliver the service and we have a contract in place that requires them to keep your information secure and not to use it for their own purposes.
How long do we keep your information?
We will hold your personal data on our systems for as long as you are a member of the League and for as long afterwards as it is in the Leagues’ legitimate interest to do so or for as long as is necessary to comply with our legal obligations.  We will review your personal data every year to establish whether we are still entitled to process it.  If we decide that we are not entitled to do so, we will stop processing your personal data except that we will retain your personal data in an archived form in order to be able to comply with future legal obligations e.g. compliance with tax requirements and exemptions, and the establishment exercise or defence of legal claims.
We securely destroy all financial information once we have used it and no longer need it.
Your rights
You have rights under the GDPR:
to access your personal data
to be provided with information about how your personal data is processed
to have your personal data corrected
to have your personal data erased in certain circumstances
to object to or restrict how your personal data is processed
to have your personal data transferred to yourself or to another business in certain circumstances.
You have the right to take any complaints about how we process your personal data to the Information Commissioner:
https://ico.org.uk/concerns/
0303 123 1113.
Information Commissioner's Office
Wycliffe House
Water Lane
Wilmslow
Cheshire SK9 5AF
For more details, please address any questions, comments and requests regarding our data processing practices to our Registrations Secretary or Chairman.
Copyright © 2014-2020 Chris Welch
